trackif.com 2016-04-17

# Privacy Policy - MyAlerts

_Last Updated: January 25, 2016_

This policy explains our information practices, defines your privacy options and describes how your information is collected and used. 

This policy covers the website at www.myalerts.com (the “MyAlerts Website”) and the various mobile and desktop applications (collectively the “Applications”) made available by MyAlerts Inc. (“MyAlerts”). The MyAlerts Website and the Applications are owned and operated by MyAlerts a corporation organized under the laws of Delaware. Should you have privacy questions or concerns, send an email to [privacy@myalerts.com.](mailto:privacy@myalerts.com)

By using or visiting the MyAlerts Website or using the Applications, you agree to the collection and use of information in the manner described in this policy. MyAlerts shall have right at any time and without prior notice, at its sole discretion, to revise this policy. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you by email, by means of a notice the next time you log in to the MyAlerts Website, by means of a notice on the MyAlerts Website homepage or when you next activate the Application. Such revisions and additions shall be effective immediately upon notice. You are responsible for reviewing the MyAlerts Website or Applications periodically for any modification to this policy. Any access or use of the MyAlerts Website or Applications by you after notice of modifications to this policy shall constitute and be deemed to be your agreement to such modifications. 

## The Information We Collect

This policy applies to all information collected on the MyAlerts Website, any information you provide to MyAlerts and any information that results from your use of Applications. You will most likely provide us personal information to us when you register as a user of MyAlerts Website, license and then use the Applications or participate in certain MyAlerts promotions or events. The personal information we may collect might include: passwords, user names, addresses, email addresses, phone numbers and credit/debit card numbers. 

## The Applications

The Applications allow users to track information about products and services and internet searches. When you use the Applications to search for products/services or save searches, the Applications enable you to automatically “track” the product/services and searches. If your tracking criteria are met (e.g. the product goes on sale, the product meets your target price point or a new search result is found), MyAlerts will notify you of such information using a variety of communication methods, including, but not limited to, push notifications, email alerts, SMS messages, browser notifications and social network messages. 

Use of the Applications is subject to the terms and conditions of the Application License Agreement (click here to review the license associated with the Applications: www.myalerts.com/applicenseterms ). 

## Blogs and Product Reviews

The MyAlerts Website or Applications may include blogs, product reviews or other message areas that allow users to post or send information to the MyAlerts Website or the Applications. When you post information to the MyAlerts Website or Applications, others can also view that information. We urge you to exercise caution when providing personally identifiable information to MyAlerts, MyAlerts Website or the Applications. 

## Our Collection of Your Data

In addition to the personal information you supply, we may collect certain information to (1) evaluate how visitors, guests, and customers use the MyAlerts Website or the Applications; or (2) provide you with personalized information or offers. We collect data to make the MyAlerts Website and Applications work better for you in the following ways: to improve the design of the MyAlerts Website and Applications, to provide personalization on the MyAlerts Website and Applications and to evaluate the performance of our marketing programs. The technologies we may use to gather this non-personal information may include “IP” addresses, “cookies”, browser detection, “weblogs” and various “geo-location” tools. 

## How we Collect and Use Information

Our primary goal in collecting your information is to provide you with a personalized, relevant, and positive experience with the MyAlerts Website and Applications. 

You can register on the MyAlerts Website or the Applications to receive promotions and updates, or to be contacted for market research purposes. In addition, if you use the Applications, MyAlerts, as part of those Applications, may send you push notifications (texts, sounds or pop-ups that are initiated without having to open the Applications), text messages, emails or other communications related to your use of the Applications. You can control your privacy preferences regarding such communications (see the section below entitled “Your Privacy Preferences”). 

From time to time, you may be invited to participate in optional customer surveys or promotions, and MyAlerts may request that you provide some or all of the above listed personal information in those surveys or promotions. We use information collected from surveys and promotions to learn about our customers in order to improve our services and develop new products and services of interest to our customers. 

IP addresses define the Internet location of computers and help us better understand the geographic distribution of our visitors and customers and manage the performance of the MyAlerts Website. Cookies are tiny files placed onto the hard drive of your computer when you visit the MyAlerts Website, so we can immediately recognize you when you return to the MyAlerts Website and deliver content specific to your interests. You may modify your browser preferences to accept all cookies, be notified when a cookie is set, or reject all cookies. Please consult your browser instructions for information on how to modify your choices about cookies. If you modify your browser preferences, certain features of the MyAlerts Website may not be available to you. 

We may detect the type of web browser you are using to optimize the performance of the MyAlerts Website and to understand the mix of browsers used by our visitors, guests, and customers. To learn about how people use our site, we examine weblogs, which show the paths people take through the MyAlerts Website and how long they spend in certain areas. 

By using the Application we will have access to (1) information related to the products/services or searches you are tracking (including, but not limited to, the product/services name, search criteria, price, SKU and product/services or search description); (2) a history of our communications related to your use of the Applications, including your actions related to such communications; and (3) information related to a product or service that you tracked using the Applications and subsequently purchased. The Applications may also include the ability to link certain geographical information made available by us with your physical location. When you use the Applications, the Applications may know, in very general terms, your current physical location. To the extent that your physical location can be determined by the Applications, we may use your location to make available information to you that is relevant because of your physical location. 

We may also compile certain general information related to your use of the Website and Applications. You agree that we are authorized to use, reproduce and generally make such information available to third parties in the aggregate, provided that your information shall not include personally identifiable information about you or be attributable to you. 

MyAlerts may contract with unaffiliated third parties to provide services such as customer communications, analytics and other services. When we do this, we may, in certain limited circumstances, provide your personally identifiable information to such third parties solely as necessary for such third parties to provide those services. MyAlerts will not provide any such information to any such third parties unless such third parties agree in writing: (a) to use such information solely for the purpose of providing such services; and (b) not to disclose, provide or make available such information to any other party. 

## Our Commitment to Data Security

Access to your personal data is limited to authorized MyAlerts staff or approved vendors. Although total security does not exist on the Internet or through mobile networks, MyAlerts shall make commercially reasonable efforts to safeguard the information that you submit to MyAlerts. 

## Use of the MyAlerts Website and Applications by Children

The MyAlerts Website and Applications are not intended for use by children under the age of 13. 

## Your Privacy Preferences

When you sign up as a registered user of the MyAlerts Website or Applications you may begin receiving marketing communications such as email newsletters, product and service updates, communications related to your use of the Applications and various promotions. Our customers generally find this type of information useful. If you do not want to receive these updates or communications, you may “opt-out” by unchecking the appropriate box on the user registration page, or should you choose to opt-out after registering, you can select the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of the text or email and follow the opt-out instructions or send an email to [privacy@myalerts.com.](mailto:privacy@myalerts.com)

## How to Access or Correct Your Information

Send MyAlerts an email at [privacy@myalerts.com](mailto:privacy@myalerts.com) if you want to access, review or correct your personally identifiable information collected by MyAlerts. To protect your privacy and security, MyAlerts require a user ID and password to verify your identity before granting you the right to access, review or make corrections to your personally identifiable information. 

## Disclosure of Information

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process. It is also possible that MyAlerts would sell its business (by merger, acquisition or otherwise) or sell all or substantially all of its assets. In any transaction of this kind, customer information, including your personally identifiable information, may be among the assets that are transferred. If we decide to so transfer your personally identifiable information, you will be notified by an email sent to the last know email address in our files, by notice posted on the MyAlerts Website or when you activate the Applications. 

## Privacy and Other Websites and Applications

The MyAlerts Website or the Applications may contain links to other websites or other mobile applications that are not controlled or managed by MyAlerts. For example, you may be routed to such websites or mobile applications by an affiliate of MyAlerts or you may be directed to a website or mobile application of a MyAlerts retail partner that offers for sale the products or services you’re tracking through the Applications. Such MyAlerts affiliates or retail partners may place on your computer a tracking device such as a “cookie” (please see the fourth paragraph of the “How we Collect and Information” above for more information about “cookies”). The information collected by such tracking devices may be used by the affiliate or retail partner to calculate fees due from MyAlerts or fees payable to MyAlerts. MyAlerts is not responsible for the privacy practices of these affiliates or partners. This policy only applies to information collected by MyAlerts. If you have any questions concerning such affiliate or retail partner’s privacy practices, please carefully review their respective privacy policies.
